<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 21:13:14 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, world!</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>wilderlab is open for business. We can help with:
 eDNA analysis Monitoring of rare and cryptic species Invasive species detection Pathogen detection and quantitation Water quality assessment High-throughput sequencing Bioinformatics Custom R package development Tagging and geospatial mapping Web applications  Please get in touch with your eDNA biomonitoring and biodetection requirements. You can contact us by email or phone (64210588068).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/faq/</guid>
      <description>We are an environmental DNA (eDNA) biomonitoring service based in Wellington, New Zealand. We specialize in biological water quality evaluation and the detection and monitoring of rare, cryptic and invasive species using new DNA sequencing technologies.
We can help with:
 eDNA analysis Monitoring of rare and cryptic species Invasive species detection Pathogen detection and quantitation Water quality assessment High-throughput sequencing Bioinformatics Custom R package development Tagging and geospatial mapping Web applications  Please get in touch with your eDNA biomonitoring and biodetection requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>wilderlab is owned and operated by Dr. Shaun Wilkinson, a molecular and computational biologist based in Wellington, New Zealand. See https://shaunpwilkinson.github.io/ for more information, or feel free to get in touch via email or phone (64210588068).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>